and welcome back to the riddles of dr. X
or minecraft edition
this is riddle number 39 and all you
have to do is pay close attention and
everything will do you be just fine so
let me go first thing to do is grab our
starter map and we're out and that's me
and I say I guess I have more in our
chests later on so don't worry about
that
we'll come back to that minecart we're
all the coaster away here on kryptonian
we pride ourselves on quality service at
our beach resort Oh which which is which
is currently closed as the nearby forest
is on fire I'm sure that'll be fine
don't worry about
oh that's that's not okay
you have to call and Ranger Rick anyway
onwards
welcome to the quarry we mined for all
kinds of important minerals in this area
let me just give you a quick quick look
and all the important parts don't worry
about what's over here
there's my buddy Kyle what's he doing oh
[Music]
hey did you set my forest on fire
I got the mountain we go
oh good just in time for sunset let's
get out here and I like to leave myself
notes as reminders of what to do around
here it's a big world anyway oh that
poor house looked like I wasn't in it
anyway it's a over sized bed for
oversized cows and let's see ah the
sunset come on lots of fall it's a
pretty big drop now oh yeah that for is
this gone now to go back I need to do
wait a minute
I need to do is hit this button I think
yeah no no what are we did this isn't
how it was it's okay we can fly this is
fine now that's nighttime so back to the
adventure line
[Music]
and what is this other line and I'm just
going to fly through this could be some
difficult terrain
[Music]
there we go this looks better Oh No is
that another fire all right clearly
we're gonna have to postpone future
editions of Minecraft riddles due to
lack of fire extinguishers on this world
but we'll get a patch out for that quite
soon and oh yes this is where I keep my
maps so now there we go now we've got an
extra map and we'll just take a look at
that it looks good to go and I hope you
paid attention thanks for solving the
riddle all you have to do is take all
the words you found in my word search
and pop them in the screen and order the
items in these boxes should be a bit of
a hint post in the comments if you know
the answer like and subscribe and good
luck